Okay. So hopefully you had the chance to try
希望你已经尝试过
out using the Network tab to inspect some of the other websites.
使用 Network 面板来检查网站
You hopefully are getting a picture for
你已经大概了解
just how many assets are on all of these websites.
这些网站的资源数量有多么惊人
I would encourage you to just continue to use that Inspect tool.
我建议你继续使用检查 (Inspect) 工具
A lot of times if I'm looking at a website and it looks really cool to me,
很多时候 当我看到一个很酷的网站
I inspect element just to see what's there.
我都会检查元素 看看有什么
I think you can learn a lot of front-end skills just doing that.
你可以通过这种方法学到很多前端技能
So continue that.
所以 勤加使用
Now that you have a picture for what kinds of
现在你已经大概了解
things we're dealing with in a professional front-end application,
一个专业级前端应用需要处理的工作
we're going to talk about what build tools are out there and what
接下来 我们将讨论都有哪些构建工具
they're actually doing to make that management easier.
以及它们如何简化资源管理
So a good definition for build tools is that they allow
构建工具是 能帮助开发者自动化处理网站资源文件的工具
saving them lots of time and headache.
节省很多时间和烦恼
This is really true.
确实如此
It's hopefully going to bring together our picture of what all of the build tools do.
通过这个定义 希望你能了解到所有构建工具的主要功能
Not any one of them specifically,
虽然不是全部
but in general, build tools are management tools.
但通常情况下 构建工具都是管理工具
They manage all of our assets.
管理着所有的资源
We need them because without a management tool,
我们需要它们 因为如果没有管理工具
all of these assets is like herding cats.
所有资源文件就像放养的猫
You're going to run around trying to manage all
当你试图一个个地管理网站上所有的资源
of your assets one-by-one and put them all into the head tag of your website,
将其全部放到 head 标签里 会忙到人仰马翻
and it's just really going to get difficult as soon as you get more than a few.
而且 随着管理的数量越大 困难程度也越高
So in order to save ourselves that craziness,
因此 为了不被逼疯
we have a lot of these tools.
我们有很多这样的工具
Some of the common names that you'll hear in build tool land are Grunt and Gulp,
在这个领域中 一些常见的工具有 Grunt 和 Gulp
Brunch, Webpack, Bower, and some of these other ones.
Brunch、Webpack、Bower 等等
There are so many that I think sometimes that's
工具太多了 我认为这有时候也是
a barrier for junior developers to get into using build tools.
入门开发人员使用构建工具时的障碍
It's kind of abstract what they do,
这些工具各自的用处有些抽象
there's so many out there that it's hard to figure out where to start.
工具种类太多了 不知道从哪里入手
Just to give you a bit of the lay of the land here,
大致地讲一下
NPM scripts are about as simple as you can go to manage website assets.
NPM 脚本是管理网站资源的最简单的工具之一
Those are just normal NPM scripts that you would put in your package.json file,
就是那些放入 package.json 文件中的普通 NPM 脚本
and you can do quite a lot with those.
这些脚本用处也很大
On the other hand, you have Grunt and Gulp,
此外 还可以使用 Grunt 和 Gulp
which are probably the most common names to hear after Webpack.
这些可能是除 Webpack 之外出镜率最高的工具了
Grunt and Gulp allow you to write simple tools,
你可以使用 Grunt 和 Gulp 来编写简单工具
simple rules that will allow you to manage all of your assets in a specific way,
通过编写一些简单的规则 就可以用特定方式管理所有资源
and they're pretty easy to set up.
而且很容易设置
Webpack is probably the most common one right now.
Webpack 可能是目前最常见的构建工具
It really rose to fame alongside of React,
随着 React、Vue 以及一些其他基于 JavaScript 前端项目的兴起而声名远播
Webpack works really well.
Webpack 确实非常好用
It is JavaScript-based itself.
它本身是基于 JavaScript 的
So when you're working with JavaScript front-ends,
因此 当你使用 JavaScript 开发前端时
you're very likely to see it.
很有可能会看到它
In fact, Webpack is used inside of the Create React app, React build tool.
事实上 在 React 构建工具 Create React App 中使用的就是 Webpack
So you might have already used it without knowing.
所以你可能在不知情的情况下已经使用过了
Here, why and how Webpack differs from other build tools.
那么 Webpack 与其他构建工具有何不同?
Webpack is becoming the ubiquitous build tool.
Webpack 正成为无所不在的构建工具
It's seen around all of these more modern frameworks,
在较为现代的框架中随处可见
and so you'll see it if you haven't already a lot.
因此 如果你还没见过的话 可能以后会经常见到了
Grunt and Gulp are slightly simpler options.
Grunt 和 Gulp 稍微简单些
They'll allow you to build rules,
仍然可以在工具里写规则
but they don't have quite all of the functionality that Webpack has.
但是功能不如 Webpack 全面
If a project is simple enough,
如果一个项目很简单
you might not need everything that Webpack does for you.
你可能不需要用到 Webpack 的全部功能
So you can keep that in mind as well.
可以记住这一点
Some of the reasons that we chose to do Webpack for this course though,
本课程选择使用 Webpack 的部分原因是
are that it is becoming so well-known in
它在前端开发领域越来越受欢迎
front-end development that it's just a really good thing for you to know regardless.
无论如何 了解 Webpack 都是有好处的
It's a little bit more complicated.
它确实更加复杂
So if you learn Webpack from the start,
因此 如果你从一开始就学习 Webpack
if you need to go back to Grunt and Gulp,
再回头学习 Grunt 和 Gulp 时
it really won't be an issue.
就会觉得很简单了
Hopefully with those two things in mind,
希望牢记这两件事
learning Webpack will be pretty easy.
学习 Webpack 会比较容易